const dayTenQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "The correct place to be wiped when wiping Khuf in ablution is to wipe …………",
    options: [
      "Over the Khuf",
      "Under the Khuf",
      "Back of the Khuf",
      "Front of the Khuf",
      "Inside of the Khuf",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Do we need to make another Tashahud after Sujud Sahwi (prostration of forgetfulness)?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "All are Sunanul fitra (the act that correspond to the nature of mankind) that we can get from authentic narration except ……….",
    options: [
      "Circumcision",
      "Letting the beard grow",
      "Tarawih in congregation",
      "Cutting the nails",
      "Shaving the pubes",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which deed is the dearest to Allah?",
    options: [
      "To offer the salats at their stated fixed times",
      "To be good and dutiful to parents",
      "To participate in Jihad (religious fighting) in Allah's cause",
      "To give sadaqah",
      "To help orphans",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Salat is called Solatul wustoh (middle prayer)?",
    options: [
      "Salatul ‘Asr",
      "Salatul Fajr",
      "Salatul Magrib",
      "Salatuz Zuhur",
      "Salatul ‘Ishaa",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "From authentic narration, in Islam, Aqeeqah (Naming…) comes up on the ……………………..day of birth.",
    options: ["8th", "7th", "3rd", "10th", "9th"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "All are beneficiaries of Zakat except …..",
    options: [
      "Those employed to collect the funds",
      "To free captives.",
      "For those in debt",
      "The wayfarer",
      "The rich",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When performing Tayammam (sand ablution), how many times do we place our hands on the ground?",
    options: [
      "one time",
      "two times",
      "three times",
      "four times",
      "five times",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Is dreaming after Istikharah a condition for its acceptance?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Is Zakat compulsory on a man that has less than 5 camels?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In sharia, a traveler can wipe over his Khuf for three days while inhabitants can wipe over it for…………",
    options: [
      "one day and one night",
      "two days",
      "three days",
      "four days",
      "seven days",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Prohibited times for voluntary Salat are …….",
    options: ["seven", "six", "five", "four", "three"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Do we need to wash the corpse of a martyr that died during battle in the cause of Allah?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Can we give out Zakat to our relatives, if they are among the beneficiaries of Zakat mentioned in the Quran?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Qasr (Shortening of Solat) together with Jam’u (Combining of Solat) is allowed for ……………",
    options: ["Sick person", "Debtors", "Traveler", "Prisoner", "Preacher"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
];

export default dayTenQuestions;
